<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <item>Who am I? Where am I from? Where am I going?</item>
    <item>Thinking is more important than action forever, no thinking action is called automatically.</item>
    <item>I do not believe in taking the right decision, I take a decision and make it right.</item>
    <item>The world of reality has its limits; the world of imagination is boundless.</item>
    <item>It is only shallow people who do not judge by appearances. </item>
    <item>Thinking is my endless country, words are I have wing prop.</item>
    <item>All change in history, all advance, comes from the nonconformists. If there had been no trouble-makers, no Dissenters, we should still be living in caves.</item>
    <item>We are all in the gutter, but some of us are looking at the stars.</item>
    <item>No matter how small and unimportant what we are doing may seem, if we do it well, it may soon become the step that will lead us to better things.</item>
    
    <item>You're never really done as long as you have a good story and some one to tell it to.</item>
    <item>The words you speak become the house you live in.</item>
    <item>As far as policy is concerned, I have to say something.</item>
    <item>Do you think you'll be able to go to sleep fight away?</item>
    <item>No communication or improper communication, sometimes can bring a lot of regret.</item>
    
    <item>My kingdom is as wide as the world，and my desire has no limit．I go forward always，freeing spirits and weighing worlds without fear。without compassion，without love，and without God．Men call me science．</item>
    <item>The person who thinks there can be any real conflict between science and religion must be either very young in science or very ignorant in religion．</item>
    
    <item>Art comes from life, the difference between ordinary people and artists is that how the art into life.</item>
    <item>Art is a higher type of knowledge than experience．</item>
    <item>I was more than a week when artist.</item>
    <item>The learned understand the reason of the art，the unlearned feel the pleasure．</item>
    <item>Art is concerned not with botany but with flowers，not with root causes，but with ultimate values，not with sex but with love，not with human nature but with human being．</item>
    <item>A true artist takes no notice whatever of the public．The public are to him non—existent．</item>
    <item>Art is I；science is we．</item>
    <item>All nature is but art，unknown to thee；
All chance，Direction，which thou canst not see．</item>
    
    <item>The heart has a grave, buried the widow.</item>
    <item>Why I have never catched the happiness? Whenever I want you ,I will be accompanyed by the memory of...</item>
    
    <item>If you are smart, don't put that person as a friend, if he and the attachment of your enemies.</item>
    <item>What's up?</item>
    <item>The best things in one's life, is the friendship with others.</item>
    
    <item>The Times 03/Jan/2009 Chancellor on brink of second bailout for banks.</item>
    <item>Who's going to talk to me about Facebook's Libra?</item>
    <item>I am a Block Chain Developer</item>
    <item>The technology behind bitcoin lets people who do not know or trust each other build a dependable ledger.</item>
    <item>Looking for Block Chain Developers</item>
    <item>Block chains convey trust between you and me</item>
    
    <item>When I was going up the stairs
I met a man who wasn't there
He wasn't there again today
I wish
I wish he'd go away</item>
    <item>Lost in oblivion,dark and silent and complete.
I found freedom.
Losing all hope was freedom.</item>
    <item>If you wake up at a different time, in a different place, could you wake up as a different person?</item>
    
    <item>Genius only means hardworking all ones life.</item>
    <item>Learning is the eye of the mind.</item>
    <item>For those who like reading, reading is a kind of enjoyment. The idea in the book is like an invisible motive force, which influences your thoughts and mentality.</item>
    <item>Reading dead books is harmful to one's own self, but not reading is not good. A good book is the blood of a great soul.</item>
    
    <item>For action, no action, no results.</item>
    <item>Life is action, not equal to death.</item>
    <item>I never worry about action, I'm more worried about the danger of not action.</item>
    
    <item>Keep your mouth shut and your eyes open．</item>
    <item>Cautious silence is the holy of holies of worldly wisdom．</item>
    <item>Silence gives consent．</item>
    
    <item>Loses the human nature, lose a lot; lost brutal, lose everything.</item>
    <item>The highest level of attention to a civilization is completely destroyed</item>
    <item>Death is a beacon of eternal light, no matter where you go, eventually you will turn to it./nEverything will die, only death eternal life.</item>
    <item>Your lack of fear is based on your ignorance.</item>
    
    <item>Deceiving others can only temporarily, but honesty is long.</item>
    <item>You a moment of good faith to win the trust of others patiently, let the good faith become a habit.</item>
    
    <item>There is nothing uncultivated，nothing sterile，nothing dead in the universe；there is no chaos，no confusion except in appearance．</item>
    <item>I am the oldest light in the universe</item>
    
    <item>Books and friends should be few but good.</item>
    <item>People die, but books never die. No man and no force can abolish memory.</item>
    <item>Reading is to the mind what exercise it to the body.</item>
    
    <item>#include &#060;stdio.h&#062;
int main() {
  printf("Hello, World! ");
  return 0;
}</item>
    <item>SELECT * FROM World WHERE Someone LIKE \'%You%\'</item>
    <item>I always thought love was an abstract class until you made an instance of it.</item>
</resources>
